Errrrrr...
Uh-oh!
No! Watch it!
Sorry, Squidward!
Oh-ho! What a cute little dolly!
He can be our drop-master, Scott, and ride with us in the cab.
Oh, great idea. Why don't I put him up front while you pick up the rest of the tracks?
Thank you, Squidward!
Mmm-hmm.
I want to have fun!
Huh?
I want to get good grades!
Whether you should stop saying one of them!
I want to destroy you!
What the f-t-a-ha!
That doll's my best!
Oh!
You gotta try it!
Forget it, you nitwit!
There's no way I'm getting in the back of that filthy wagon!
Duh!
Ow!
Now you turn the lorry-again!
Hey, look! We f-t-a-ha!
Isn't this cozy?
Please let this nightmare end.
Get out of the way!
Whoa!
He did a good job!
A teeny-bottom looks so clean now!
Just one more house and I can finally say goodbye to this trash life!
Let's get these in the truck and get out of here!
Hey!
Get away from my stuff!
Oh, this isn't stuff, Patrick! It's cut!